よしっ！　はい　はい　はい　はい。
Yes!
Go! Go! Go!
There goes all my spending money for the month.
今月のお小遣いの残り
全部使ったのに→
私って　何をやっても　ダメダメ…。
No matter how hard I try...
（ミゼルカ）はい。
あっ。
Here.
どうぞ。
うん。
It's yours.
lost te saguri de sagashiteta
Lost, trying to find it blindly with my hands.
tozasareta mirai no kotae nante doko ni mo nai
But the key to the locked future is nowhere to be found.
hashiru shoudou ima kaidoku funou
Undecipherable urges surging.
found kudaketa hazu no unmei wo
I found the fate I believed broken.
mijukuna yume no naka de kikoetekitan da
I heard it in my immature dream.
saigo made I'll be there for you
I'll be there for you till the very end.
tachitomaranai kono hari dake wa
I can't stop. I hear nothing else.
boku no asu wo kizamu oto tsukisasu
How this needle carves my future.
shinjitsu kara nigetara ima
I'm running away from the truth now.
genjitsu ni mo maketara ima
I'm losing to reality now.
nani ga nokoru no (nokoru no)
What will be left?
kazoekirenai kono kizu dake ga
The countless scars on my body
boku no kinou wo zanzou toshite kataru
are the only thing telling the story of my past.
unmei ga hodokete mo ima
Even if fate falls apart now,
sonzai wo kowashite mo ima
even if existence shatters now,
boku no michi wo yuku yo
I'm walkng down my own path.
It's now or never.
This is what they say: "Live your life today."
There will always be, there will always be a way.
Smiley's Trap
（アナ）アナが思うに　オルペウス・リングって
いろんな種類があったんだね！
I think... there are many kinds of Orpheus rings out there!
（キュービック）うん。　僕も驚きだ。
Yeah. It's quite a surprise.
詳しいことは　今
イヤリングの残骸を調べてるけど…。
I'm trying to figure out the details by analyzing what's left of the earring.
（ギャモン）…つうより　あんなもの
素人につけさせるなんてよ！
But how can they give that shit to normal people?!
なにもんだ？
あの「オルペウス・オーダー」ってのは！
Who the hell are these Orpheus Order guys?
（ノノハ）うん。
確か「偉大なるオルペウスを信奉し→
They said they "follow the great Orpheus,
卑劣なる神々のくびきから
人間を解放せんとする者」って。
and aim to free humankind from its cowardly gods."
神々の…　くびき…。
Cowardly gods?
回想　（バロン）
そうです。　「人類は　その頭脳の
聡明さを神々に疎まれ→
Indeed.
"The gods shunned the power of the human mind,
回想
本来の能力を
封じられた存在である」。
thereby sealing our true potential."
回想
そんな思想を　連綿と
受け継いできた古来よりの結社→
The Orpheus Order is an organization who has believed in this teaching since ancient times.
回想
それが…　オルペウス・オーダー。
回想　（ソウジ）封じ込められていた
能力の解放が　彼らの目的ですか？
They want to release that sealed potential?
回想
ええ。　そして　人に
全能の力をよみがえらせる。
Yes, thus awakening the true power of mankind.
回想
彼らが　カイト君に接触してきたのは
それを達成するためだと？
And that's why they contacted Kaito?
回想
詳しくは　私にも…。
I don't know the details either.
ただ　喜ばしい理由でない
回想
ことだけは確かでしょう。
However, it's clear they're not doing it out of kindness.
回想
なにせ　オルペウス・オーダーは
道を誤っていた頃のＰＯＧ以上に→
It would seem that they're even more violent than the POG was in its misguided days.
回想
過激な集団のようですから。
てめえの欲のために　パズルで
不幸を生み出そうとしてる→
So they're just assholes who cause misery with puzzles for their own goals!
やつらってわけか！
（アイリ）ああ～　こぼしちゃいました。
（食堂のオヤジ）だから　言っただろう。
Oh no, it fell!
That's why I said you shouldn't take so much at once!
一度に　そんなに　たくさん
持っちゃ　危ないって。
ごめんなさ～い。　ヘヘヘヘッ。
I'm sorry.
（食堂のオヤジ）ほらほら
片づけるから　どいて　どいて！
Move along and I'll clean it up.
（アイリ）本当に　ごめんなさい。
手伝います。
I'm really sorry! I'll help!
さては　あいつら！
I'll get them for this!
どういうつもりよ！　あんたたち！
（武田）誤解です。
What the hell were you thinking?!
You're misunderstanding!
うん？！
（相沢）５階　家具売り場です。
And you're supposed to be Miss Understanding!
何が誤解だ！
Misunderstanding my ass!
ホントなんです！　全員分　運ぶって
私が言いだしたんです～！
It's true! I offered to bring them their lunches!
えっ？！　そうなの？
You did?
パズル部は今　ジュニア・パズル・ワールドカップ
目指して　猛特訓中なんです。
The puzzle club is training really hard for the Junior Puzzle World Cup.
みんな　お昼休みも
ずっと頑張ってて。
They're even practicing during lunch break.
だから　ごはんの用意くらいは
私が…。
So I thought the least I could do was bring them lunch.
何言ってんのよ。　アイリちゃんだって
パズル部の部員じゃない。
What are you saying? Aren't you a club member as well?
私…　パズル作るのも　解くのも
全然　上手にならないから…。
I'm not good at solving or making puzzles.
本当　何やってもダメですよね
私って…。
No matter how hard I try...
エヘヘヘッ。　ああ　そうだ！
Oh right! I should go buy them some drinks!
みんなの飲み物
買い出しに行かなきゃ！
それじゃ　ノノハ先輩　失礼します！
See ya later, Nonoha!
あぁ　困ったときは　声かけてね！
手伝うから！
If you ever need any help, just call me and I'll be there!
ありがとうございます。
う　うっ　あ～！
Thank you very much!
Ow!
あぁ　痛たたたっ！
大丈夫？！
Are you okay?
慣れてますから。　ヘヘヘッ　うわ～っ！
（転ぶ音）
I'm used to it...
エヘヘヘッ。
また転んじゃった。
I fell again...
回想
（フリーセル）君は　このくらいじゃあ
思い出さないかな。　僕の事なんて。
I guess you won't remember me from just this much.
俺は　やつに
心の声
会ったことがあるのか？
Have I met him before? When? Where?
いつ？　どこで？
心の声
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
（アイリ）はぁ～。
やっぱり　今の私なんかじゃ…。
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
National Elementary School
Puzzle Tournament Local Preliminaries
Second Place
I guess no matter how hard I try...
回想
（ミゼルカ）そうなのかしら？
私は思うな。
Really?
I don't think so.
回想
あなたは　ちょっぴり
優しすぎるだけ。
You're just too kind.
ん？
回想
力を持っていないんじゃない。
You don't lack strength.
心の奥にしまい込んでる。
回想
You've just locked it in your heart.
このリングは　おまじない。
That ring is a charm.
あなたが　本当の力を
回想
発揮できますように…。
It will help you bring that strength to the surface.
The strength I've locked in my heart...
心の奥に　しまい込んだ力…　か。
Sum
Puzzle
Takeda's Puzzle
Airi Clear
The sum puzzle too!
（武田）足し算クロスも！
（相沢）苦労するのに。
It was so hard!
Number
Area
Takeda's Puzzle
Airi Clear
The number area too!
（武田）ナンバー・エリアも！
（相沢）なんばしょっと！
What's going on?!
（武田）ブロック分割も～！
（相沢）このブロックは　何？
Block
Finder
Airi Clear
Takeda's Puzzle
The block finder too!
She always finds a way!
まさか！
ジュニア・パズル・ワールドカップ用に→
No way!
You solved the puzzle Naoki made for the Junior Puzzle World Cup in under a minute!
ナオッキーさんが　渾身込めて作った
パズルを…　１分もかけずに…。
ごめんなさい！　アイリ　本当の力
見せつけちゃった～！
Sorry! I started taking it seriously!
そんなのアイリ～。
You're kidding me!
すごい！　すごいぞ　アイリ～！
Amazing! You're amazing, Airi!
（男子４人）
そいや！　そいや！　アイリ！　アイリ！
Go! Go! Airi! Airi!
武田さ～ん！
はっ！
Takeda!
Yes!
ノドが渇いたわ。
はは～っ！
I'm thirsty!
Yes, ma'am!
アイリさまの大好物
缶入りおしるこが　こちらに！
I have brought you the canned soup which you are so fond of!
プハー！
ちょっと～！
なんで　こしあんなのよ！
Why is it the strained bean one?!
おしるこって言ったら
粒あんに決まってるでしょう！
I obviously wanted the ground bean one!
す　すぐに買い直してきます！
もう　使えないんだから。
I will buy a new one right away!
You're hopeless.
アイリちゃん？！
あっ　ノノハ先輩　どうしました？
Airi...
Oh, Nonoha! What's up?
それは　こっちのセリフ。
アイリちゃんこそ　どうしたの？
That's what I want to know.
What happened to you?
え～？　どうもしませんよ。
Why would you ask that?
ただ　本当の自分　隠しているの
やめただけです。
I just stopped hiding my true self.
本当の…　自分？
Your... true self?
そうだ。　ちょうど　よかった！
先輩　お願い　聞いてもらえますか。
Yes. Oh, this is just perfect!
I have a bit of a request for you.
だって　言ってくれたじゃ
ありませんか…。
Didn't you say I could always ask you for help?
困ったときには　声をかけろって。
信じらんねえな…。
I can't believe it.
悪い夢でも　見てたみてえだ。
It's like it was just a bad dream.
Anyway, Nonoha's late!
…ってか　ノノハのやつ　遅っせえな。
新作スイーツの味見　つきあえ…　とか
言ってたくせによ。
She asked to meet me here so I could taste her new sweets.
アイリちゃんてば　困ったことって
言うから　何かと思ったら…。
Airi said she needed help, but why do I have to come here?
あの人は…。
That woman...
ん？！　上？
Upstairs?
（ミゼルカ）ウッフッフ。
ったく…　いつまで待たせんだよ。
ノノハは？
Dammit, how long is she gonna keep me waiting?
（武田・相沢）そいや！　そいや！
せいや！　せいや！
そいや！　そいや！
あ～　はぁ？
Daimon Kaito! Lady Airi summons you!
大門カイト！
アイリ様が　お前に用があるそうだ。
Huh?
To Kaito
Airi
アイリのやつ　こんなとこに
呼び出して　一体　何の用だ？
Why did Airi call me here?
（モニター画面）「カイト先輩！」。
うわっ！　アイリ？！
Kaito!
Airi?
「私　今までずっと　ドジで　のろまで
何をやっても　ダメダメだったけど→
Until recently, I've always been a buffoon and a dimwit
no matter how hard I tried.
今日で　そんなアイリから
卒業します！→
But starting today, I'll become a different person!
というわけで　先輩にも
お手伝いしていただきますね！」。
And you're going to be helping me with that.
て　手伝い？！
With what?
「大門カイト！
私のパズルに挑戦しなさ～い！」。
Daimon Kaito! Challenge my puzzle!
Huh?
「あれ？」。
あぁ。
（せきばらい）
「大門カイト！　私のパズルに挑戦…。→
Daimon Kaito! Challenge my...
あれ…　あの…」。
Huh?
なんで　俺が　お前と
勝負しなきゃなんねえんだよ。
Why do I have to fight you?
「決まってるじゃありませんか。
パズルで　カイト先輩を倒せば→
It's obvious!
If I beat you with a puzzle, no one will make fun of me anymore!
もう　誰も　私のこと
バカになんて　できないでしょう」。
誰も　バカになんかしてねえよ。
No one's making fun of you anyway.
「カイト先輩。
もし　挑戦してくれない場合は→
Kaito...
If you won't challenge the puzzle, something dear to you will get hurt.
先輩の　とっても大切なものが
傷つけられちゃうかも」。
大切なもの？
Something dear to me?
「あの着ぐるみの中に
何が入っていると思います？」。
What do you think is inside that doll?
お前…　あっ！
What the...
あれは！
That's it!
オルペウス・リング！
心の声
じゃあ　アイリも　やつらに…　心を？
An Orpheus ring! They got to Airi too!
「うふっ」。
まさか…。
Don't tell me...
You'll challenge it, right?
「挑戦　受けてくれますよね？→
パズルは　このパソコンに出題します。→
I'm sending the puzzle to that computer.
５×５マスのスペースの中央に
『ぺろりんぽろりん』のブロックがあります。→
In the middle of this 5x5 grid, there is a Smiley block.
その周りに　私が　邪魔物のブロックを
積み上げるので→
I will be placing other blocks around it to get in your way.
カイト先輩は　パソコンで　クレーンを操作し
邪魔物ブロックをどけて→
You must use the computer to control the crane
and get rid of the blocks in the way to free Smiley.
指定する手数以内に『ぺろりんぽろりん』を
助けだしてください。→
簡単でしょ？　ただし…→
It's simple, isn't it? However...
クレーンを一度操作するたびに
『ぺろりんぽろりん』の着ぐるみが→
Whenever you move the crane, the Smiley doll will get closer and closer to the ground.
少しずつ地面へと下がります」。
「もし　指定した手数内に
パズルが解けないと…」。
If you can't solve the puzzle in a certain number of steps...
「どうです？　私のパズル
気にいってもらえました？」。
What do you think? Do you like my puzzle?
くそっ！
「うふふっ」。
Dammit!
イッ。　上等だ…。
Fine! I'll save both of you!
みんな　まとめて
俺が　救い出してやる！
パズルタイムの　始まりだ！
It's puzzle time!
「手数は３回！　う～ん。　アイリ
実力　発揮しすぎちゃったかも！→
You have three moves.
I might have gone a bit overboard with my true power!
でも　これくらいじゃなきゃ　カイト
先輩も　チャレンジのしがいがないです」
But any less would be too easy for Kait—
Three moves, right?
ホントに３回で　いいんだな？
「えっ？！」。
３。
（クレーンの音）
Three.
「えっ？！　えっ？！　え～っ？！」。
２。
「あ～ああ！　ストップ！　スト～ップ！」。
Two.
Stop! Stop!
That puzzle was a mistake!
「今のパズルは　間違い！
本物は　こっち！」。
This is the real one!
はぁ？！　…んなの　ありかよっ！
You can do that?
「ありなんです！
今度の手数も３回！」。
I can!
You have three moves again!
えっ？！　ここ…　どこ？
Where... am I?
う～ん！　へっ…　３！
Three.
２！
（ブザー）
Two.
「あ～ああ！　こ　これも間違い！」。
That was a mistake too!
おい　またかよ…。
This again?
ちょっと！　ここ　どこなの？
出しなさいよ！
Hey! Where am I? Let me out!
（アイリ）「次は　これよ！」。
Here's the next one.
３！　２！
（ブザー）
Three. Two.
勘弁してくれよ。
Give me a break already!
（ミゼルカ）「いつもと　勝手が
違うみたいねぇ。　大門カイト」。
This is quite out of the line, isn't it, Daimon Kaito?
お前は…。
「でも　急いだほうがいいかも。→
You're...
But you should hurry.
オルペウス・リングが　どれくらい
人間の脳に負担をかけるか…→
You know how much strain the Orpheus ring can put on the brain.
あなたになら　分かるはず」。
うっ！
She's telling the truth, Kaito!
（キュービック）その女の言っている事は
本当だよ。　カイト！
お前ら！
Guys!
ようやく　イヤリングの残骸の解析が
終わって　分かったんだ！
I found out when the analysis of the earring finished!
If this keeps up, the ring will take control of Airi!
このままじゃ　アイリは
リングに飲み込まれる！
「しかも　そのリングは　あなたが
勝利しないと　外れない仕組み」。
And it can't be taken off unless you win.
（ミゼルカ）「さあ　あなたが
パズルを解くのが先か→
Which one will be first? Will you win or will the ring take control?
それとも　彼女が壊れてしまうのが
先か…　フフフッ…」。
「私は　カイト先輩に
勝ちたいんだもん…。→
I want to win against Kaito...
勝って　誰からも
バカにされないように→
So that no one can make fun of me anymore!
認めてもらえるように
なるんだもん…　もう。→
So that people will recognize me...
So... So...
だから…　だから…」。
That many blocks... in only four moves?
これだけの数のブロックを
たった４手で…。
（キュービック）解けるわけない！
That's impossible!
「フフ…　フフフフ…　フフフフフフッ！→
うっ」。
アイリ！
Airi!
まずいよ　ギヴァーが意識を失った以上
このパズルは　もう撤回できない！
This is bad!
With the Giver unconscious she can't withdraw this puzzle!
ここままじゃ…。
どうする？　カイト…。
At this rate...
What are you gonna do, Kaito?
Someone!
誰かぁ～！
俺に解けないパズルは　ねえ！
There's no puzzle I can't solve!
カイト～！
Kaito!
解けたぜっ！
（ノノハ・キュービック）あっ？！
Solved it!
そうか！　一度の手数で→
I see! You can move multiple blocks per move!
複数のブロックを
まとめて　つり上げるんだね。
思うに　さすが　カイト！
I think... that's Kaito for you!
アイリを頼む！
Take care of Airi!
あっ？！　なんじゃ　こりゃ～！
What the hell?!
ノノハじゃ…　ねえ…。
It's not Nonoha!
これって　カイトの大好きな
「銀河パズル警察　ポリキューブ」。
It's the "Galactic Puzzle Police: Policube" you love so much!
Dammit!
そいや～！
ノ　ノノハ…　お前…。
N-Nonoha? What the...
あっ　はぁ。　テーペロ。
Tee-hee.
テ　テーペロ…。
Tee-hee...
ウッフッ…。　おかげで
すばらしいデータが取れたわ。
We've obtained lots of wonderful data because to you.
ありがとう　井藤ノノハさん。
Thank you, Itou Nonoha.
（アイリ）え～っ？！　あの人
ノノハ先輩に　そんなことを？！
She did that to Nonoha? I didn't ask for that!
私　そんなの　頼んでないです！
ただ　教室に　忘れ物を
取りに行ってほしいって…。
I just asked Nonoha to take something from the classroom for me.
分かってる。
気にすんな。
I know.
Don't worry about it.
腹ん中にしまい込んだ
思いなんてのは　誰にでもある。
Everyone has feelings that they won't allow to surface.
むかつくのは　それを表に引きずり
出して　悪用した　あいつらだ。
It pisses me off that those guys force those feelings out and misuse them.
私　どんなことされても
ノノハ先輩を利用しようだなんて→
I would never use Nonoha like that, no matter what they did to me!
絶対に思いません…。
ありがとう。
Thanks.
まっ　俺も　とんだ早とちり
しちまったわけだし。
Well, I was jumping to conclusions too.
でも　一番大切なものって聞いて
カイトってば　そんなに私のことを…。
So when they were talking about something dear to you, I was the first thing you thought of?
ちげ～よ。
あの着ぐるみ　見た瞬間→
That's not it!
When I looked at that doll, it reminded me of you!
お前が　頭に浮かんだだけ
えっ？！
だっつ～の。
I don't make such eccentric faces, right?
ねえ　私　あんなに
エキセントリックな顔してないよね？
でも　私は「ぺろりんぽろりん」
大好きですよ！
But I love Smiley!
あっ　否定は　しないんだ。
あの微妙な　かわいさが…。
Well, I can't deny it.
It's oddly cute in a way.
えっ？！　微妙？　私って　微妙なの？
Odd? I'm odd?
微妙つ～か　奇妙。
奇妙？！
Not odd, unique.
Unique?
（相沢）ペヘペロ～！　本日の
缶入りおしるこは　こちらに！
Pee-hee...
We have brought you today's soup!
粒あんに加え　ずんだに　くりあん
かぼちゃあん　全て→
In addition to the ground bean, we brought green bean, chestnut, and pumpkin as well!
All with bean jam of course!
あん入りでございます。
もう　結構ですから…。
You can stop now...
Do you have any other orders, Lady Airi?
では　何か別のご用命を！
（２人）アイリ様～！
え～っ？！
（２人）アイリ　アイリ　アイリ。
Airi! Airi! Airi!
（相沢）ほれ　ほれ　エヘヘヘッ。
（武田）アイ　アイ　アイ！
（２人）アイリ様～！
Airi!
いや～ん！　勘弁してくださ～い！
Leave me alone!
eiyuu kidori itsu datte shinjita muteki no kankaku
I think I'm a hero and believe that I'm invincible.
tatakatte iru no wa chikyuu no tame nanka janai
I'm not fighting for the world.
motto mai peesu de
It's for a more personal,
sou motto shoujikina negai no tame
a more honest wish.
nando to naku kizutsuite mo
No matter how many times I'm hurt